Guide to the Ithaca Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender Task Force records, 1984-2005.
Ithaca Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender Task Force records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Ithaca Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender Task Force records, 1984-2005.
7571
Ithaca Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender Task Force.
4.9 cubic feet
Correspondence, publications, records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, press releases, original layouts, and other working files from the publication of "OUTLINES: A Newsletter for Ithaca's Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Community," from the first issue, Dec. 1984 to #23, April/May 1989, and from 1993-1998. Plus, the Ithaca Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender Task Force's publication of local businesses and organizations and mailings sent to members, 1991-2005 (incomplete). One issue of the Big Red Rag.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, press releases, original layouts, and other working files from the publication of "OUTLINES: A Newsletter for Ithaca's Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Community," from the first issue, Dec. 1984 to #23, April/May 1989, and from 1993-1998. Plus, the Ithaca Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender Task Force's publication of local businesses and organizations and mailings sent to members, 1991-2005 (incomplete). One issue of the Big Red Rag.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Ithaca Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender Task Force.; Popow, Jeff.
Titles:
Outlines (Ithaca, N.Y.)
Subjects:
Lesbians--Political activity--New York (State); Gays--Political activity--New York (State); Lesbians' writings.; Gays' writings.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Assorted Files: 1993-1998
  - Master List of Advertisers (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Grammar Rules--Staff (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Please Add Us to Your Mailing List (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Change of address forms, September, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Staff lists, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - STAP-- Women's Safer Sex Survery (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Ad Rates (fliers) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Advertisers addresses (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - GLB group listings (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - STAP (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Media Packets--originals, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - April budget/circulation summary, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Agendas for meetings (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Meetings--current issue, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Resource Office brouhaha, April 1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Haworth Press, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Leather S/M Newsletter, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - AFCU round-off, July 1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Media Packets--samples, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Budget, annual report, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Old Advertisers, September 1996 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Contracts, signed and returned, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Accelerated Voice--personals (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Preparation of 1996 budget, April 1997 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Contract renewal packets, April 1996 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Fliers--Spring 1997 mailing, February 1997 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Fliers--Fall 1997 mailing, August 1997 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Fliers--Winter 1997 mailing, November 1997 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Coffeehouse Schedule, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Fliers--May 1996 mailing (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - ImageOut Film Festival, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Kinko's Order Forms, Other Info (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Meetings, handouts, January 1998 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Outlines expanding flier, January 1998 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Goals for 1998 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Dawn Manor Retreat Center (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Rainbow Connection for Men (Cortland) (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Syracuse Gay and Lesbian Chorus (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - LGB Resource Office, Cornell (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Flier--Accepting Personals, November 1997 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Fliers in Winter issue, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Alternatives Federal Credit Union (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Sources of GLB Information (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Change of Address Notices, August 1997 onward (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Post-It-Notes, "Be on Mailing List?", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Phone Tree Flier, February 1998 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Fliers with Spring 1998 issue (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Chief Basile December 1997 Coffeehouse (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Fliers--Winter 1997 Mailing (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Fund-Raiser Flier (late March 1998) (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - A Celebration of Black History Month, no date (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - A Fatal Accident, no date (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Afro-American and White American Women- Culture, Community, and Organizing, no date (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Medical Update, no date (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Patients and Foodborne Illness, no date (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - An Interview with Author Penny Hayes, no date (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - An Open Letter to My White American Gay and Lesbian Friends, no date (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Article Drafts, no date (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Ask Queenie, no date (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Breaking the Silence- Lesbian Battering, no date (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Does the Right Thing- Finally, no date (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Election Opinion, no date (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Empathy, Not Sympathy, no date (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Event Calendars, no date (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 15 Things You Can Do When a Friend Has AIDS, no date (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Heart Beat- Luppies Make Prime-Time, no date (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Hooray for A.A., no date (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - How People Grieve, no date (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - ILGTF Forms Lesbian and Gay Speakers Bureau, no date (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Ithaca- Domestic Partnership Ordinance, no date (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Karen Silverstein, no date (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Lesbian Resources, no date (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Lesbian Safe Sex, no date (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Making It With Mary, no date (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Mick Ellis, no date (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Mike Miller, no date (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - The Neighborhood Crisis Prevention Hotline, no date (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Outlines/ILGBTF Mailing List, no date (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Outlines- Women's Space, no date (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Out of the Closet and Into the Stacks, no date (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Possible Indicators of Chemical Dependency, no date (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Sappho Appears at CGs, no date (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Sexuality Archive Comes to Cornell, no date (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - 'Tis the Season for Softball, no date (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Tompkins County Task Force for Battered Women, no date (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Valentine's Day Inserts, no date (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - When Statistics Become Real- Bias-Related Violence, no date (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Who's Cruising Who?, no date (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - YEAH! (article), no date (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Your Own Backyard/The Campaign to End Homophobia, no date (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Zapping- An Electrifying Hazard, no date (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Keeping a Community Together, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - March Perspectives, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Quotes of 1987 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Tompkins County Democratic Party Platform, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Outlines/ILGTF, 1987-1990 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Bioherb, Inc., 1988 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Calls for Submissions, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - CMV Retinitis, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Cornell Cinema, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Persona Review, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Picnic Protest- An Open Letter to the Ithaca Gay and Lesbian Community, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Poetry Submissions, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Quilt Fact Sheet, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Surveys, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Community- Newsletter of the Capital District Lesbian and Gay Community Center, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - CU Sexuality Archives Position Filled, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - News Articles, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Outlines- Noteworthy News, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Pamphlets, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - AIDS, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Event Fliers and Invitations, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Ithaca Times, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Press Releases, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - AIDS, Pentamidine, and Lyphomed, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Chosen Books, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Herizon Newsletter, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - The Ithaca Fair Practices Ordinance- Making It Work, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - 1989 Ithaca Women's Softball Schedule (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - NY State Lesbian and Gay Lobby, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Office of the Mayor- San Francisco- Unmarried Partners Bill Signed, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Pete's Cayuga Bar- Policy Statement, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Photographs and Postcards, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Quotes of 1989 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Resource Guides, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - San Francisco Examiner (1), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - San Francisco Examiner (2), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Stonewall, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Syracuse Herald American- Newspaper, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Notes, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Printing Orders, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Proposed Law on Bias-Related Violence- New York, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Outlines- Draft Pages, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Outlines Magazine Drafts, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 87)
- Series II. Ithaca Lesbian/Gay/Bisexual Task Force Calendars
  - November, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - March, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - May, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - April, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - October, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - November, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - December, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - January, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - February, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - March, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - April, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - May, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - June, July, August, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - September, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - October, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - November, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - December, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - January, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - February, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - March, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - April, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - May, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - June, July, August, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - September, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - October, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - November, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - December, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - January, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - February, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - March, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - April, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - May, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - June, July, August, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - September, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - October, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - November, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - December, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - January, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - February, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - March, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - April, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - May, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - June, July, August, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - September, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - October, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - November, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - December, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - January, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - February, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - March, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - April, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - May, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - June, July, August, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - September, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - October, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - November, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - December, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 103)
- Series III. Press Releases
  - Press Releases, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 104-107)
- Series IV. Outlines Archive
  - Advertising Contracts, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Miscellaneous articles, publications (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Post office information (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Projected revenues, May 1993 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Ads--old, not running February 1994 issue (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - New logo ideas (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Mykill cartoons: good copies (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Cartoons (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Coffeehouse schedules, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Fliers for Outlines mailings, September 1994 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Advertising Contracts, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Guidelines for submissions, old (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Contracts renewal packets, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Survey to advertisers, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Record of payments, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Very old instructions, invoices (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Old advertisers, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Circulation summary/inventory (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Contracts, signed and returned, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Contracts, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - David Bianco (writer), January 1996 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Price quotes, January-February 1996 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Contract renewal packets, June, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Thank yous--not signed, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - GLB Youth--Weitzen (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Fund-raising mailing, April 1996 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Flier December ILGBTF mailing, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Articles never used--filed February, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Schedules, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Schedules, abbreviated, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Borealis flier, April 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Outlines meeting, April 7, April 1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pride agenda mailing, July 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Suzanne Reiner: ILGBTF non-profit status--presentation to board, June 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Schedule, summer 1997-spring 1998, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Series V. 1996 Fund-Raiser
  - Final tally of donations, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Comment forms, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Address changes, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Receipts, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ad rate sheets, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Letters, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Comment forms, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Fliers for donation follow up, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Annual reports, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Series VI. 1997 Fund-Raiser
  - Final tally of donations, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Comment forms, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Receipts, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Sample packets, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Fund-raising April originals, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Donation form, comment form, thank you, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Letters, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Thank yous, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Post-It-notes, August mailing, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Fund raising letter, August 27, August 1997 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Labels, return envelopes, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Series VII. 1998 Fundraiser
  - Fund-raiser cover sheet, February 1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Receipts, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Tally of donations, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Thank yous, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Donation forms, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Return envelopes, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Series VIII. Articles and Source Materials
  - Fall articles, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Winter source material, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Spring articles, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Summer articles, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Fall articles, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Winter articles, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Spring articles, originals, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Summer articles, originals, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Interested in advertising again?, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Fall articles/advertising information, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Winter articles, advertisements, source materials, etc., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Series IX. Outlines Correspondence
  - Correspondence, etc., 1993 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, etc., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 44-45)
  - Correspondence, etc., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 46-48)
  - Correspondence, etc., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 49-51)
  - Correspondence, etc., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 52-58)
  - Correspondence, etc., 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, etc., 1998 (Box 8, Folder 2-11)
  - Correspondence, etc., 1999 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Series X. Information From Other Organizations
  - "Queer Survivors: A Conference on Abuse and Sexual Identity" (Lesbian Gay Bisexual Resource Office--Cornell University), November 1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Pride Agenda Flyer "Governor Pataki Vetoes Historic $2 Million in Lesbian and Gay Health and Human Services Funding from the State Budget", 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Speakers List(Cornell University Lesbian, Bisexual and Gay Studies), Spring 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - "Don't Miss It!" (Empire State Pride Agenda) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual Awareness Month at Cornell: Gaypril '92 Calendar, April 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - March for Women's Lives (Tompkins County NOW), April 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Night of 100 Parties/Annual Brunch (Empire State Pride Agenda), February 1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Leadership Training for people who are actively working on LGBT issues or who would like to be.(Empire State Pride Agenda), May (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Common Ground, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Community (Albany) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Pride Inside (Syracuse) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Amethyst (Binghamton) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - AIDS Work (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Cinema, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Firebrand Books (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Haworth Press (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Human Rights Campaign (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Human Services Coalition of Tompkins County (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Human Sexulaity Collection (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Kitchen Theater (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - LGCN (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - New York Folklore Society (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Planned Parenthood (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Rowe Conference Center (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Suicide Prevention and Crisis Service (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Syracuse Gay and Lesbian Chorus (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Task Force for Battered Women (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Series XI. Back Issues of Outlines
  - Outlines: December, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Outlines: February, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Outlines: April, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Outlines: June, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Outlines: September/October, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Outlines:September/October, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Outlines: November/December, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Outlines: April/May, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines: November/December, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines: Summer, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines: Winter Eternal, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines: May, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines: February/March, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines: February/March, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines: December, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines: September/October, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines: February/March, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines: November/December, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines:September, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Outlines: February/March, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Outlines: April/May, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Outlines: Summer, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Outlines: December/January, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Outlines: February/March/April, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Outlines: April/May/June, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Outlines: June/July/August, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Outlines: Fall, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Outlines: Winter Eternal, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Outlines: February/March, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Outlines: November/December, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: June/July, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: April, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: June/July, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: April/May, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: Summer, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: September/October, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: February/March/April, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: April/May/June, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: June/July, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: September/October, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: Summer, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: September/October, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: December/January, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Outlines: Summer, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Outlines: Fall, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Outlines: Winter, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Outlines: Spring, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Outlines: Summer, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Outlines: Fall, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Outlines: Winter, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Outlines: Spring, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Outlines: Summer, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Outlines: Fall, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Outlines: Winter, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Outlines: Spring, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Outlines: Summer, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Outlines: Fall, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Outlines: Winter, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Outlines: Spring, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Outlines: Summer, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Outlines: Fall, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Outlines: Winter, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Outlines: Spring, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Outlines: Summer, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Outlines: Fall, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Outlines: Winter, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Series XII. Original Layouts
  - Letters 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Typing Instructions, Notes, Typesetting, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Layout Pages and Graphics, no date (Box 1)
  - Outlines #1, December 1984 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #1, December 1984 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #2, February 1985 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #2, February 1985 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #2, February 1985 (Box 3)
  - Outlines #3, April 1985 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #4, June 1985 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #5, September/October 1985 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #6, November/December 1985 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #7, February 1985 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #8, April 1986 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #9, June/July 1986 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #10, September/October 1986 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #11, November/December 1986 (Box 1)
  - October #12, February/March 1989 (Box 1)
  - Outlines #13, April/May 1987 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #13, April/May 1987 (Box 3)
  - Outlines #14, Summer 1987 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #14, Summer 1987 (Box 3)
  - Outlines #15, September/October 1987 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #15, September/October 1987 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #15, September/October 1987 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #15, September/October 1987 (Box 3)
  - Outlines #16, Winter 1988 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #17, February/March/April 1988 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #18, April/May/June 1988 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #19, June/July/August 1988 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #20, Fall 1988 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #21, Winter 1988 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #22, February/March 1989 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #22, February/March 1989 (Box 2)
  - Outlines #23, April/May 1989 (Box 2)
  - Summer 1993--Outlines--originals (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fall 1993--Outlines--originals (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Winter 1993--Outlines--originals (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Spring 1994--Outlines--originals (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Summer 1994--Outlines--originals, also Stonewall 25 fliers, originals, samples (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Fall 1994--Outlines--originals (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Winter 1994--Outlines--originals (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Spring 1995--Outlines--originals (Lizard ad. Removed, page 4, used on Summer 1995) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Summer 1995--Outlines--originals (Ads removed: Lizard page 23 on Fall 1995; Gay Gospel Music page 16 used on Winter 1995) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Fall 1995--Outlines--originals (Removed ads: STAP page 9; relationship counseling page 17; Snyder page 9) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Winter 1995--Outlines--originals (Missing many ads) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Spring 1996--Outlines--originals (Removed Yahn ad page 4) (Box 9, Folder 12)